<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Sam and Will as Nomads</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Sam and Will as Nomads</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Jan 18-24: Fernie, BC</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/jan17-24_fernie/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/jan17-24_fernie/</guid><description>Post 3: Family in Fernie Next stop on this cross Canada skiing journey was Fernie, BC. This small town of roughly 5 thousand people in the summer which doubles in the winter is home to my cousin, Penelope, her husband Mat and their son, my first cousin once removed (a mouthful, I know), Nolan. It is also home to a beautiful ski resort which thankfully for me, offers a wider range of terrain compared to Kicking Horse and so more ways to ease myself into west coast black diamonds.</description></item><item><title>Jan 7-17: Golden, BC</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/jan11-17_golden/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/jan11-17_golden/</guid><description>Post 2: Kicking Horse Between January 10th and 17th, Will and I had our first week-long stay in Golden, BC. We have purchased an Epic Pass for our skiing adventures, and with said pass we had 7 days of skiing each at all RCR mountains (which includes Fernie, Kicking Horse, Kimberley, ect).
Views 👀 Previous Next  The original plan: Ski 4 days between Kicking Horse, Revelstoke (2 hour drive away) and Lake Louise (1 hour drive away).</description></item><item><title>Jan 6-10: Video</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/jan6-10_video/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/jan6-10_video/</guid><description> </description></item><item><title>Jan 6-10: Driving Out</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/jan6-10_drive_out/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/jan6-10_drive_out/</guid><description>Post 1: The Drive Out to BC On January 4th, Will and I completed our last day of paid work for the better part of 2022. The sabbatical (aka mini retirement) that we had been planning pretty much since our first date (in October of 2017) was finally becoming a reality. The original plan was to leave on January 5th at night and drive up to Bracebridge, followed by a 13h drive to Thunderbay the next day.</description></item></channel></rss>