<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Sam and Will as Nomads</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Sam and Will as Nomads</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>June17-28: Biarritz pt.4</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/june29-july25_biarritz4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/june29-july25_biarritz4/</guid><description>Post 25: Biarritz, A Reflection This post will be slightly different. Since Will and I weren’t gallavanting the world over the last month and instead were fully embracing a retired lifestyle we have less to report on an activity basis and more to discuss in terms of conclusions (we had lots of time to reflect).
Having two months in one location with no job was a new experience. One we’re so happy we had, it spurred new thoughts and realizations.</description></item><item><title>June17-28: Video</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/june17-28_video/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/june17-28_video/</guid><description> </description></item><item><title>June17-28: Biarritz pt.3</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/june17-28_biarritz3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/june17-28_biarritz3/</guid><description>Post 24: Biarritz with Family The visit of old roommates continued a few days after Kaelan and Liam left with the arrival of my parents.
In the few days before my parents arrived, Will and I begged our airbnb host for a fan to brave the impending heat wave (35+ degrees heat we would experience for over 3 days), and mercifully, it arrived a day later. We successfully set it up (though didn&amp;rsquo;t use all the screws) and it was essential in helping us sleep through the next few nights.</description></item><item><title>June10-16: Video</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/june10-16_video/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/june10-16_video/</guid><description> </description></item><item><title>June10-16: Biarritz pt.2</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/june10-16_biarritz2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/june10-16_biarritz2/</guid><description>Post 23: Biarritz with Friends Kaelan and Liam came to visit us for a week. And we were stoked to get to share our little oasis with them. Though they did arrive a little/very jet lagged.
Note: Kae and Liam both brought film cameras. And the results from the realms of film are a wonderful encapsulation of the week. I&amp;rsquo;ll showcase them in a separate bonus post - make sure you check them out 📷!</description></item><item><title>June10-16: Biarritz pt.2 Bonus</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/june10-16_biarritz2_bonus/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/june10-16_biarritz2_bonus/</guid><description>Post 23.5: Film Photography I struggled with all the amazing pictures that were taken over the week. But here are some of my favourites from the film cameras:
Previous Next Here are Kae and Liam taking a nap, beer in hand because the jet lag hadn&amp;rsquo;t quite left their system. Here Will and I are sharing ice cream that is melting incredibly fast. This photo was taken on the beach at Saint-Jean de Luz.</description></item><item><title>June1-9: Video</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/june1-9_video/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/june1-9_video/</guid><description> </description></item><item><title>June1-9: Biarritz pt.1</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/june1-9_biarritz/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/june1-9_biarritz/</guid><description>Post 22: Biarritz Baby 🏄🏼‍♀️ 🏄🏽‍♂️ We made it to Biarritz. The place I’d been dreaming about since I visited in July 2017 and promised myself all those years ago, that I would come back, for longer than a week and learn to surf. I find this town magical, a perfect juxtaposition of beautiful, rich architecture with nomadic surfers.
The plan was to settle in Biarritz for 3 months (essentially the whole summer).</description></item><item><title>May 29-31: Paris</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may29-31_paris/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may29-31_paris/</guid><description>Post 21: Jetlag in Paris After almost 2 months in Australia and New Zealand, it was time to venture back somewhat closer to home. On May 28th, we were officially entering Phase 3 of our sabbatical: Biarritz and Europe.
It started off with the longest travel day I’ve ever experienced. We left Auckland at 8pm on May 28th, and flew a redeye to San Francisco (12hrs flight), before taking yet another redeye to Paris (11hrs flight).</description></item><item><title>May21-24: Video</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may21-24_video/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may21-24_video/</guid><description> </description></item><item><title>May25-28: Video</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may25-28_video/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may25-28_video/</guid><description> </description></item><item><title>May 21-28: NZ North Island</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may21-28_nz_n1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may21-28_nz_n1/</guid><description>Post 20: Entering Middle Earth Our campervan was swapped out for a small toyota hybrid, which was really nice given the price of gas (hovering around 3NZD/L). Fun fact, New Zealand base gas is at 91 octane, and it can go as high as 100 in some places (warned that it’s not good for all cars, lol).
We drove straight from Auckland to Matamata, settled into a little garage airbnb, that was very cute, but the bathroom was in another shed, so we had to yet again go outside in the middle of the night to use the bathroom…</description></item><item><title>May18-19: Video</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may18-19_video/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may18-19_video/</guid><description> </description></item><item><title>May 17-20: NZ South Island pt.4</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may17-20_nz_s4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may17-20_nz_s4/</guid><description>Post 19: Completing the Loop Though we had completed the biggest hikes of our South Island itinerary there was still so much to see. Our initial plan was to drive all the way around the island, going through Nelson, down the east coast and back to Christchurch. [Plug for my interactive map!]
But given we had spent an extra day in Queenstown and we were trying to learn from past overplanning mistakes, we decided we would cut across Arthur&amp;rsquo;s Pass to head back across the island and keep a slower pace.</description></item><item><title>May16-17: Video</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may16-17_video/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may16-17_video/</guid><description> </description></item><item><title>May14-16: Video</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may14-16_video/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may14-16_video/</guid><description> </description></item><item><title>May13: Video</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may13_video/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may13_video/</guid><description> </description></item><item><title>May 12-16: NZ South Island pt.3</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may12-16_nz_s3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may12-16_nz_s3/</guid><description>Post 18: New Favourite Hikes We drove from Milford Sound to Wanaka on May 12th, with a mandatory stop back in Queenstown to play disc golf and get more ice cream. I didn’t particularly like disc golf, discs don’t throw anything like frisbees, and having Will meticulously counting attempts added to the frustration. So we moved to a new model, Sam doesn’t count her shots and can cheat whenever (the same way I play golf actually), and Will counts his score and plays by all the rules.</description></item><item><title>May9-11: Video</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may9-11_video/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may9-11_video/</guid><description> </description></item><item><title>May 7-11: NZ South Island pt.2</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may7-11_nz_s2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may7-11_nz_s2/</guid><description>Post 17: An Autumn May Birthday From the Catlins we were supposed to drive to the iconic Milford Sound area, spend two nights there giving us enough time for a birthday boat ride and a hike. Thankfully though Will took a look at the weather forecast and it was supposed to be POURING (like over 125mm of rain per day) in Milford Sound over May 7-9. Given we had no accommodations booked and our boat ride was changeable we changed course.</description></item><item><title>May4-9: Video</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may4-9_video/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may4-9_video/</guid><description> </description></item><item><title>May 4: Video</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may4_video/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may4_video/</guid><description> </description></item><item><title>May 3-6: NZ South Island pt. 1</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may3-6_nz_s1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/may3-6_nz_s1/</guid><description>Post 16: Settling into a van It will be hard to encapsulate our time in New Zealand with my limited ability with words. Campervaning in the south island for over 2 weeks has been a highlight of the trip, and non-ironically, my life. The collection of South Island Blog posts will not be short - apologies in advance.
If you want the crash look at what we&amp;rsquo;ve done, I&amp;rsquo;ve put together a map of our route!</description></item><item><title>Apr 29-May 2: Video</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/apr29-may2_video/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/apr29-may2_video/</guid><description> </description></item><item><title>Apr 29 - May 2: Melbourne</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/apr29-may2_melbourne/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/apr29-may2_melbourne/</guid><description>Post 15: Final Australian City For our last stop in Australia we were lucky enough to be hosted by Melbourne’s newest residents, Hill and Riggs, friends of ours from Toronto working from Melbourne for the next year (and possibly more - it’s an ongoing debate 😅).
Melbourne is another incredibly vibrant city. We had an absolute blast visiting and playing tourist. We went to see an Aussie Rules Football game which was incredibly entertaining.</description></item><item><title>Apr 24-28: Video</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/apr24-28_video/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/apr24-28_video/</guid><description> </description></item><item><title>Apr 24-28: Whitsundays</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/apr24-28_whitsundays/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/apr24-28_whitsundays/</guid><description>Post 14: Rain or Shine We made the decision to head up to the Whitsundays even though the forecast called for rain. We figured if we had a nice airbnb with a view, it would still be nice to relax in warm rainy weather. And I was very much looking forward to the plan being “relax”. Will and I have learned that if you don’t plan for explicit relaxation/chill days, then you don’t get them.</description></item><item><title>Apr 20-23: Video</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/apr20-23_video/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/apr20-23_video/</guid><description> </description></item><item><title>Apr 20-23: Brisbane</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/apr20-23_brisbane/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/apr20-23_brisbane/</guid><description>Post 13: Maria and Koalas After spending 4 days in Brisbane, Will and I concluded that Maria was right. Brisbane is a fantastic city to live in but could probably be done in 1 day if you didn’t know anyone in the city. However, Will and I were lucky enough to know a local who showed us the best time and allowed us to crash in her one bedroom apartment. We owe you one, Maria.</description></item><item><title>Apr 11-19: Video</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/apr13-19_video/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/apr13-19_video/</guid><description> </description></item><item><title>Apr 11-19: Sydney</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/apr13-19_sydney/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/apr13-19_sydney/</guid><description>Post 12: Traveling to the other side of the world Leaving Canada for Australia was just a series of unfortunate events. Here are the bullet points to our sob story:
We were scheduled to leave for Melbourne on Thursday april 7th. Given we had both caught covid in the states we each needed a doctor&amp;rsquo;s note clearing us for travel, which were a small headache to obtain. We get to the airport to realize that, duh, we need a visa to enter Australia, but no worries it should only take 10min to obtain.</description></item><item><title>Mar 18-31: The Drive Back</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/mar18-31_drive_back/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/mar18-31_drive_back/</guid><description>Post 11: There and almost back again. A tale of travel in 2022. I should have been writing this post from the comforts of a Montreal cafe. But alas, it was not meant to be.
On March 18th we set out to drive back across the US over 4 days, stop in to visit friends in Philadelphia, NYC and Vermont before crossing the border back to Canada on March 28th. The drive back itinerary was chosen by optimizing for roughly 7hrs driving days and cheap accommodations close to the highway.</description></item><item><title>Mar 5 - 17: Video</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/mar5-17_video/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/mar5-17_video/</guid><description> </description></item><item><title>Mar 5-17: Colorado</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/mar5-17_colorado/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/mar5-17_colorado/</guid><description>Post 10: Converging in Colorado We wrapped up the ski season in Colorado, with 4 final mountains: Beaver Creek, Breckenridge, Keystone and a little known resort called Vail. Fun fact which I learned on this trip, after finding out that one of the founders of Vail (Peter Seibert) was a veteran of the 10th Mountain Division, who fought in Italy during WWII, is that downhill skiing owes its origin in large part to military endeavours (a way to get around more easily in cold mountainous regions).</description></item><item><title>Mar 3 - 4: Video</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/mar3-4_video/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/mar3-4_video/</guid><description> </description></item><item><title>Mar 3-4: Utah</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/mar3-4_utah/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/mar3-4_utah/</guid><description>Post 9: Utah Rocks! Though I do hope some people enjoy reading these (often long) blog posts, I will try and keep this one short and encourage everyone to go watch the video Will compiled. It gives a much better idea of the beauty and thrill of these parks. Especially given that describing these trails in words is beyond my artistic ability.
Zion National Park This park should be on everyone’s bucket list.</description></item><item><title>Feb 25- Mar 2: Video</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/feb25-mar2_video/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/feb25-mar2_video/</guid><description> </description></item><item><title>Feb 25-Mar 2: SF -> LA</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/feb25-mar2_california/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/feb25-mar2_california/</guid><description>Post 8: California Dreaming Well if I thought Vancouver was warm in February it is not even comparable to the coast of California. We were finally able to put the shorts we brought to good use! We spent a weekend in San Francisco before driving down Highway 1 to LA over 2 days. The stunning views were endless.
San Francisco (Not to be called San Fran…) We spent a wonderful weekend with Will’s uncle Eric and his husband Philip in their beautiful home in San Francisco.</description></item><item><title>Feb 16-24: Video</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/feb16-24_video/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/feb16-24_video/</guid><description> </description></item><item><title>Feb 16-24: Lake Tahoe</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/feb16-24_lake_tahoe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/feb16-24_lake_tahoe/</guid><description>Post 7: Entering Heaven The plan: Skiing the 3 mountains we had access to with our epic pass in the region (Heavenly Lake, Kirkwood and North Star).
The reality: Our airbnb was minutes from a chairlift in Heavenly but an hour of winding roads to both Kirkwood and North Star. Naturally we were more inclined to ski Heavenly, and after multiple conversations with strangers on chairlifts, we concluded that Kirkwood was worth a visit and that we could comfortably skip North Star.</description></item><item><title>Feb 12-15: Video</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/feb12-15_video/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/feb12-15_video/</guid><description> </description></item><item><title>Feb 12-15: Border Crossing</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/feb12-15_border_crossing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/feb12-15_border_crossing/</guid><description>Post 6: Crossing that border Our next major destination was Lake Tahoe, our airbnb was reserved on the Nevada side for Feb 16th. We knew we were leaving the hospitality of Will’s family in Vancouver on the 13th, but until the 12th, we didn’t yet know where we were going to stop along our drive. We crafted a plan over lunch at the Naam in Kitsilano. We would sleep our first night in Astoria, Oregon.</description></item><item><title>Jan 30-Feb 11: Video</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/jan30-feb11_video/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/jan30-feb11_video/</guid><description> </description></item><item><title>Jan 30-Feb 11: Whistler, BC</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/jan30-feb11_whistler/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/jan30-feb11_whistler/</guid><description>Post 5: Whistler Whistler Whistler Whistler… where to begin.
Whistler is one of the biggest ski resorts in North America, it attracts 2M visitors a year (says the first hit on google). We stayed in a small townhouse type complex in Creekside, for 13 nights. Will skied 12 days, and I skied 11.
For those not familiar with this ginormous mountain, it is composed of two peaks: Whistler Mountain and Blackcomb (which merged in 1997).</description></item><item><title>Jan 25-29: Rossland, BC &amp; Vancouver</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/jan25-29_red_van/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/jan25-29_red_van/</guid><description>Post 4: Will has Family Too Over the next week we would complete our drive out to the coast, officially completing the westward drive, but beforehand we had another family stop to make in Rossland, BC, home of Red Mountain and Will’s first cousin once removed Margie and her husband Robert.
Margie &amp;amp; Robert’s Hospitality We were absolutely spoiled in Rossland for 4 days. We owe Margie and Robert a huge thank you for housing us, feeding us, entertaining us with stories, showing us the mountain and the town.</description></item><item><title>Jan 11-27: Video</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/jan11-27_video/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/jan11-27_video/</guid><description> </description></item><item><title>Jan 18-24: Fernie, BC</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/jan17-24_fernie/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/jan17-24_fernie/</guid><description>Post 3: Family in Fernie Next stop on this cross Canada skiing journey was Fernie, BC. This small town of roughly 5 thousand people in the summer which doubles in the winter is home to my cousin, Penelope, her husband Mat and their son, my first cousin once removed (a mouthful, I know), Nolan. It is also home to a beautiful ski resort which thankfully for me, offers a wider range of terrain compared to Kicking Horse and so more ways to ease myself into west coast black diamonds.</description></item><item><title>Jan 11-17: Golden, BC</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/jan11-17_golden/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/jan11-17_golden/</guid><description>Post 2: Kicking Horse Between January 10th and 17th, Will and I had our first week-long stay in Golden, BC. We have purchased an Epic Pass for our skiing adventures, and with said pass we had 7 days of skiing each at all RCR mountains (which includes Fernie, Kicking Horse, Kimberley, ect).
Views 👀 Previous Next The original plan: Ski 4 days between Kicking Horse, Revelstoke (2 hour drive away) and Lake Louise (1 hour drive away).</description></item><item><title>Jan 6-10: Video</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/jan6-10_video/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/jan6-10_video/</guid><description> </description></item><item><title>Jan 6-10: Driving Out</title><link>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/jan6-10_drive_out/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://swillasnomads.github.io./posts/jan6-10_drive_out/</guid><description>Post 1: The Drive Out to BC On January 4th, Will and I completed our last day of paid work for the better part of 2022. The sabbatical (aka mini retirement) that we had been planning pretty much since our first date (in October of 2017) was finally becoming a reality. The original plan was to leave on January 5th at night and drive up to Bracebridge, followed by a 13h drive to Thunderbay the next day.</description></item></channel></rss>